[{"answer": "INANS: Well, it causes, it triggers memories for me, pleasant memories.", "docId": "120217pmt", "aSentId": 89, "question": "Hearing Whitney sing a song say \"Don't Cry for Me,\" what goes through your mind when you hear that?", "qSentId": 88}, {"answer": "I wrote this song and CeCe singing it.", "docId": "120217pmt", "aSentId": 97, "question": "And you wrote this song?", "qSentId": 96}, {"answer": "Well, the truth about Whitney, let's go back with me and family, the last 26 years of her life.", "docId": "120217pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "As somebody who knew her really well, what is the truth about Whitney in the last 10 years, do you think?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "I think the shock is great because we walked through, I think a darker valley five, 10 years ago.", "docId": "120217pmt", "aSentId": 147, "question": "Were you as shocked as other people about what happened to her, in the sense of -- was there a sense of inevitability that Whitney wouldn't lead a long life given the lifestyle that she had chosen for herself?", "qSentId": 146}, {"answer": "She tried to run away from it.", "docId": "120217pmt", "aSentId": 157, "question": "Did she find superstardom very hard to deal with?", "qSentId": 156}, {"answer": "Aretha Franklin repeated a few people, Baby Face came in here earlier this week and told me this too, one of the big blows to Whitney was when she went to the Soul Train Awards in the early '90s and she was booed for the first time by an audience because they had had enough of Whitney.", "docId": "120217pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "And when you understand that reality, you don't want that, you know?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "Yes, I remember that time.", "docId": "120217pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "Do you remember that time?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "She's good.", "docId": "120217pmt", "aSentId": 197, "question": "Is she OK?", "qSentId": 196}, {"answer": "I think it's important.", "docId": "120217pmt", "aSentId": 214, "question": "How do you feel about it?", "qSentId": 213}, {"answer": "I think I could go right back to that lyric in \"Don't Cry for Me\" where she sings, no one is to blame, my death was meant to be.", "docId": "120217pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "How much blame is it fair to (INAUDIBLE)?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "You know, you're funny.", "docId": "120217pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "Did you ever doubt that she loved Bobby Brown?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "Well, I'll be very honest,.", "docId": "120217pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "Did you ever try to save her, perhaps on herself, when it came to the drugs?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "Not nervous at all, because when you talk about Stevie, you talk about someone that used to live around the corner from me in Detroit, Michigan, when you talk about Aretha, you're talking about Auntie Rere (ph), when you talk about these people, these are people that we were blessed to meet early on and we became family.", "docId": "120217pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "How are you feeling about this?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "I'll -- honestly I'll be thinking and this is -- this is full circle for me because the first day we met, she was opening for Jeffrey Osborne.", "docId": "120217pmt", "aSentId": 278, "question": "When you get up to sing, what will you be thinking about when it comes to Whitney?", "qSentId": 277}, {"answer": "We need to remain vigilant, always.", "docId": "120217pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "What can you tell me about this?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "Seventy two.", "docId": "120217pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "Nine times eight?", "qSentId": 353}, {"answer": "I'm doing great.", "docId": "120217pmt", "aSentId": 365, "question": "Roger, how are you?", "qSentId": 364}, {"answer": "Correct.", "docId": "120217pmt", "aSentId": 375, "question": "So you had that dream, too?", "qSentId": 374}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "120217pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "Be honest -- and you've got to be absolutely honest with me -- did you know how good he really was?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "I would like to say because I played myself and because I have a pretty good eye for talent.", "docId": "120217pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "Because you played yourself?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "He's very outgoing.", "docId": "120217pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "Does he pick his nose or what happens?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "He is, I mean, he's legitimate.", "docId": "120217pmt", "aSentId": 431, "question": "So I mean, he is the genuine deal, isn't he?", "qSentId": 430}, {"answer": "Well, I have had too many really to --.", "docId": "120217pmt", "aSentId": 440, "question": "What is the single biggest offer you have so far had for Jeremy Lin?", "qSentId": 439}, {"answer": "We haven't -- I'm not being vague, because what we haven't done is we really haven't vetted an offer that we have been really, really serious about to this point.", "docId": "120217pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "Just hard ready?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "That's very possible.", "docId": "120217pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "Two million?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "Very possible.", "docId": "120217pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "Higher?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "I have had offers in that range.", "docId": "120217pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "You have had higher offers?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "I am.", "docId": "120217pmt", "aSentId": 477, "question": "You must be enjoying this, aren't you?", "qSentId": 476}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "120217pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "Is this the greatest moment of your career?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "No, I didn't want them to take it badly in the first place.", "docId": "120217pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "Do you want them to take it better?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "I mean --", "docId": "120217pmt", "aSentId": 529, "question": "Too easy, isn't it?", "qSentId": 528}, {"answer": "Yes, yes.", "docId": "120217pmt", "aSentId": 532, "question": "That's what they call a home run, you know?", "qSentId": 531}, {"answer": "Well, again, I don't -- I don't go for people -- things about people they can't help.", "docId": "120217pmt", "aSentId": 539, "question": "Do you know if he finds it funny?", "qSentId": 538}, {"answer": "Of course I do.", "docId": "120217pmt", "aSentId": 565, "question": "Do you have a moral code yourself?", "qSentId": 564}, {"answer": "Well, you can't.", "docId": "120217pmt", "aSentId": 568, "question": "How would you define it?", "qSentId": 567}]